APPLICATION AT FINDY
Documents for your online-application
You need the following documents for the online application (PDF preferred):
Curriculum vitae (C.V.)
Other documents, e.g, diplomas, certificates, overview of grades, graduation diploma (collected to one PDF preferred).
Please note that a letter of application / cover letter is not mandatory anymore and can be uploaded optionally.
To speed up the review of your documents, please upload all relevant documents together at the same time.
Services of our job portal
The online recruitment tool offers the following services:
Search for relevant jobs matching your profile
Add your profile and apply via the online recruitment tool
Look at and update the information you stored on our system at any time
Activate the alert system so that you are informed about new openings as they occur.
Track the status of your online application 
Choose your preferred language
Send jobs offers via Facebook by using the " tell a friend " function
Use the contact form and ask questions
